<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Loginform</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bottomnavigation">bottomnavigation</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bottomnavi">bottomnavi</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Disprine">Disprin Tablet is an antiplatelet drug which is used to prevent clots in blood vessels and also relieves pain and inflammation.!</string>


    <string name="Panadol">
    Panadol  Tablets is a mild analgesic and antipyretic, and is recommended for the treatment of most painful and febrile conditions, for example, headache including migraine and tension headaches, toothache, backache,</string>


    <string name="Brufin">
       Brufen Syrup is indicated for its analgesic and anti-inflammatory effects in the treatment of rheumatoid arthritis ankylosing spondylitis, osteoarthritis and other non-rheumatoid arthropathies.</string>


    <string name="Polyfax">Use the ointment twice a day unless your doctor tells you otherwise. Only apply it to the areas of skin which are infected</string>


    <string name="Pyodine">Povidone iodine topical is used on the skin to treat or prevent skin infection in minor cuts, scrapes, or burns. </string>


    <string name="NoKuff">ND Kuff Syrup is used in the treatment of cough. It thins mucus in the nose, windpipe and lungs, making it easier to cough out.</string>
    <string name="Mucaine">Mucaine Gel Syrup is a Syrup manufactured by Pfizer.
        It is commonly used for the diagnosis or treatment of Hiatus hernia, Stomach ulcer, Inflammation of food pipe, Inflammation of stomach.</string>
    <string name="Nilstat">NILSTAT is a trade name for the antifungal medicine, Nystatin.
        Nystatin is used to treat a condition called oral candidiasis or thrush. This is an infection in the
        mouth caused by the fungus Candida and is marked by sore, creamy-yellow, raised patches in the mouth.</string>
    <string name="Humuline">Humulin 70/30 is a mixture of 70% Human Insulin Isophane Suspension and 30% Human Insulin Injection (rDNA origin) </string>
</resources>